TAYLOR FINKLEA

DEVOPS AND INFRASTRUCTURE MANAGER

CONTACT

Kansas City, KS 66109

913-414-9496

taylor.finklea@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin. com/in/taylorfinklea-8614238b/

QUALIFICATIONS

- · Management and Leadership
- 10 years of IT Experience
- 4 years of DevOps Experience
- Kubernetes and Helm
- Azure Management
- SOC II Type II Audit
- Frontend and Backend Development
- Active Directory and Group Policy
- MDM
- Powershell and Bash Scripting
- Azure Sentinel

ATTRIBUTES

- Management
- Leadership
- Eagle Scout
- Organized
- Dependable
- Eager to Learn
- Hard-Working

CERTS/AWARDS

CompTia A+
CompTia Network+
Site Development Associate CIW

Computer Technology Sterling Scholar

Woods Cross High School

PROFILE

I have a variety of experience and am the Manager of DevOps, Infrastructure and Information Security in my current role. I manage internal Infrastructure, DevOps, Kubernetes, Automation, MDM, SIEM, Audit, IT Budget, Azure Cloud and all other systems. I mentor and train members of my team.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DevOps and Infrastructure Manager

Lumifi Cyber Inc | Feb 2019 - Present

- Duties include Architecting Scalable DevOps, Management, Audits, Infrastructure, Infosec
- Architected fully scalable infrastructure using Azure DevOps, Terraform, Helm, Kubernetes,
 Packer, Windows Virtual Desktop, Azure App Gateway, Azure WAF, Azure Firewall, Azure Virtual WAN, Azure ADDS
- Organized and completed many large-scale projects, such as a full data center migration to Azure
- Manage departments of DevOps, Infrastructure and Information Security
- Working with:

Node.js

- Management/Leadership DevSecOps Kubernetes Helm Charts Github Actions Rancher Agile Methodology Github Codespaces CI/CD Pipelines Azure DevOps o AKS/EKS/GKE o K3s/RKE2 Docker o Terraform o Packer o Ansible o Git Vagrant
- Prometheus
 Microsoft Azure/AWS/GCP
 Microsoft 365
 Active Directory/Azure AD
 Grafana
- Linux/Linux Servers
 Windows Servers
 Azure CLI
 System/Network Admin
 Tailscale
 TypeScript/JavaScript

Bash/PowerShell

Postgresql/Mysql/Influxdb

○ Change Management ○ SOC II Type II

Systems Administrator / Project Manager

Executech Inc. | Aug 2017 - Feb 2019

- IT consultant working for multiple government clients
- Duties include Systems Administrator, Network Administrator, Information Security, Linux Administrator
- Managing large-scale projects
- Preparing clients for large-scale email migrations, domain migrations, and firewall migrations

Support Engineer

DigiCert Inc. | Aug 2015 - Aug 2017

- · Assigned SSL Certificates, Client Certificates, and Code Signing
- Installed, troubleshot, and configured web servers such as IIS, Apache, and Tomcat
- Answered customer chats, emails, and phone calls

IT Support Technician

Dixie State University | Nov 2014 - Aug 2015

- Answered calls, voicemails, emails for Helpdesk and for Tech Support line
- Took on work orders for customer problems, set up appointments and fixed issues
- Re-mirrored and set up new computers and equipment.

Remote Desktop Support Technician

ManagerPlus Solutions | Mar 2014 - Apr 2015

- Answered technical calls and emails
 - Troubleshot servers, networks, and our software